<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content id="ws_3203196475" name="upb Equipments Modif. And NPC Recruit Services" author="netUpb" description="      In addition to assigning modifications to your ships that you specify in the settings, it also allows you to recruit personnel of the faction and gender you want to your ships. You can also purchase some special items with the sales inventory.&#13;&#10;[b]&#13;&#10;      Note:[/b] When the player lands on the equipment dock, wharf, or shipyard platform (whether an npc or player stations). The technical officer will be present in the station's executive room for interview options.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[h1]# Attention![/h1]&#13;&#10;[list]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;  [*] [h3]You may need to disable UI Protection mode (&quot;Settings&quot; -&gt; &quot;Extensions&quot; -&gt; &quot;Protected UI Mode&quot;) before you can see the manager screen.[/h3]&#13;&#10;  [*] [h3]To access the manager or settings screen, the 'upb_lua_loader' mod (ver. 2.00) must be installed.[/h3]&#13;&#10;  [*] [h3]If you are using 'Mod Support Api Community Edition' you may have problems opening windows.[/h3]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[*][b]Compatible for x4 6.xx, 7.10 and 7.50[/b]&#13;&#10;[b]Note:[/b] There is a preview versions on the [url=https://www.nexusmods.com/x4foundations/mods/1464?tab=files]nexus mode page[/url] that fixes compatibility.&#13;&#10;[*] [b]other way for options screens can be accessed from the upb_Mods menu by talking to the NPC or player owned ships pilot.[/b]&#13;&#10;[/list][b]&#13;&#10;[/b]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[h2]# What the officer can do[/h2]&#13;&#10;[list=1]&#13;&#10;[*]In line with the options in the settings, it is possible to select the ships docked at your station and make changes in bulk.&#13;&#10;[*]The most comforting thing for the player is that modifications will be automatically added to each ship produced at the stations and arriving for repair or update,  in line with the options in the settings.&#13;&#10;[*]Transfers the NPCs you specify to the ships of your choice in your sector. (including ships that do not dock at the station in the region)&#13;&#10;[*]It has its own sales inventory. Especially the raw materials required to prepare Emp bombs are offered for sale. (Different inventory can be added according to requests from players.)&#13;&#10;[/list]&#13;&#10;[b]Extra:[/b] Added menu option to installed upb_Mods. In this way, you can also access the menus of the other modes I have written.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]Note:[/b] I re-used some characters that were previously used in the game (whose rig structures I found to be correct).&#13;&#10;      If you do not want it included, you can delete the '[b]\extensions\upb_equipmentmod_and_recruit_srv\libraries\charactergroups.xml[/b]' file.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[h2]** UPB MODs. Access Options:[/h2]&#13;&#10;    There are 5 different methods to access UPB MODs.&#13;&#10;    !!! If the option is not opened with the first 4 steps, you are probably using another mod that adds menu options. &#13;&#10;[list]&#13;&#10;[*]1- Talk to NPC ship captains.&#13;&#10;[/list]          it will appear in the bottom left (#3) position.&#13;&#10;[list]&#13;&#10;[*]2- Talk to any player ship captain or player station managers.&#13;&#10;[/list]          Under the more option, if no other mod has added it to the menu options, it will appear in the left (#2) position.&#13;&#10;[list]&#13;&#10;[*]3- Talk to Player fleet commander or ship captain if not in the fleet.&#13;&#10;[/list]          a- if there is a &quot;..more. (Mods)&quot; option, that is, if ECM (Extended Conversations Mod v0.20 on Nexus) is installed, it is in this menu.&#13;&#10;[list]&#13;&#10;[*]4- Talk to any subordinate ship in the player's fleet.&#13;&#10;[/list]          a- if there is a &quot;..more. (Mods)&quot; option, that is, if ECM (Extended Conversations Mod v0.20 on Nexus) is installed, it is in this menu.&#13;&#10;          b- Otherwise it will appear in an empty slot (#3) in the menu. ( ! unless another mod(s) has added this menu option. )&#13;&#10;[list]&#13;&#10;[*]5- In this case, use the 'Upb Equipment Modification And Reqruit Service' Mod. &#13;&#10;[/list]          This new mode assigns a Spec officer you can talk to when you land at the shipyard or wharf (player or npc) stations. &#13;&#10;          To access UPB MODs, talk to Spec. Officer Nurcan ARIKAN HOS.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[h2]# Türkçe[/h2]&#13;&#10;[h2]# Açıklama[/h2]&#13;&#10;      Gemilerinize ayarlarda belirlediğiniz modifikasyonları atama işlerinin yanı sıra gemilerinize istediğiniz faction ve cinsiyette personel alımı sağlar. Ayrıca satış envanteri ile bazı özel eşyaları satın alabilirsiniz.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;      [b]Not:[/b] Oyuncu ekipman iskelesine, wharf veya tersane platformuna indiğinde (ister bir npc ister oyuncu istasyonları olsun), teknik subay röportaj seçenekleri için istasyonun yönetici odasında bulunacaktır.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[h1]# Dikkat![/h1]&#13;&#10;[list]&#13;&#10;[*][b]x4 6.xx, 7.10 ve 7.50 sürümler için uyumludur.[/b]&#13;&#10;[b]Note:[/b] Bu modun eski sürümlerine [url=https://www.nexusmods.com/x4foundations/mods/1464?tab=files]nexus mode page[/url]﻿  sayfasından ulaşabilirsiniz.&#13;&#10;[*]Ayar ekranlarının diğer bir yolu, NPC veya oyuncunun sahip olduğu gemi pilotu ile konuşarak upb_Mods menüsünden erişilebilir.&#13;&#10;[/list]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[h2]# Subayın Yapabilecekleri[/h2]&#13;&#10;[list=1]&#13;&#10;[*]Ayarlardaki seçenekler doğrultusunda bulunduğunuz istasyona yanaşmış gemileri seçip, değişikliklerini toplu olarak yapmanız mümkündür. &#13;&#10;[*]Oyuncu açısından en rahatlatıcı şey ise istasyonlarda üretilen, tamir veya güncelleme için gelen her gemiye ayarlardaki seçenekler doğrultusunda modifikasyonlar otomatik olarak eklenecek olmasıdır.&#13;&#10;[*]Belirlediğiniz NPC'leri sektörünüzdeki seçeceğiniz gemilere aktarır. (bölgedeki istasyona yanaşmayan gemiler dahil)&#13;&#10;[*]Kendi satış envanteri vardır. Özellikle Emp bombalarını hazırlamak için gerekli olan hammaddeler satışa sunuluyor. (Oyunculardan gelen isteklere göre farklı envanter eklenebilir.)&#13;&#10;[/list]&#13;&#10;[b]Ekstra:[/b] Yüklü diğer upb_Mod'lara ait menü seçeneği eklendi. Bu sayede diğer yazdığım modların menülerine de ulaşabilirsiniz.&#13;&#10;[b]Not:[/b] Oyunda daha önceden kullanılan bazı karakterleri (rig yapılarını düzgün gördüğüm) tekrar kullanıma açtım.&#13;&#10;     Dahil edilmesini istemezseniz '[b]\extensions\upb_equipmentmod_and_recruit_srv\libraries\charactergroups.xml[/b]' dosyasını silebilirsiniz." version="151" date="2025-09-23" save="false" lastupdate="1758649449">
  <!-- upb Lua Loader -->
  <dependency id="ws_3265629547" version="201" optional="false" name="upb Lua Loader"/>
</content>
