<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff>
	<add sel="/language">
		<page id="993512" title="ship_argon_xl_battleship_ziz" descr="ship_argon_xl_battleship_ziz" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Ziz</t>
			<t id="2">(Ziz) {993512,4}</t>
			<t id="3"> At the end of the Terran Conflict, the Argon Federal Navy, Which deeply felt that Titan class destroyer were behind the times, So they publicly tendered new ships. In the Federal Navy Command, There were two opposing views on the specific performance requirements of new ships. One faction believed that expensive and difficult to maintain were the main drawbacks of the Titan class, and that new warships should be improved with ease of production and low cost, while the other faction believed that, In order to confront the powerful navy of terran, it was necessary to produce more advanced ships. The first view led to the design of the Behemoth class, But second plan is fraught with difficulties. The project of newly ship named the Lyra Project, completed its preliminary design at JSDD and awkwardly discovered that it was necessary to achieve the required technical specifications far beyond what the federal government could provide at the time and resulting in slow progress, The subsequent attack on JSDD's headquarters caused the project to stagnate and ultimately terminated due to a loss of contact with JSDD's headquarters after the gate closure incident. After the reconnection of the jumpgate, the Federal Navy discovered that the behemoth class destroyer it could produce was an antique ship from the era of the Terran Conflict. The subsequent Paranid Civil War and the Battle against Xenon also exposed a large number of shortcomings of the behemoth. By chance, while cleaning up outdated data, the Federal Data Center discovered pre design data and scattered component data that had been preserved many years ago. After analysis, The Federal Navy's Technical Services Department was pleasantly surprised to find that the seemingly impossible warship at the time was not only very suitable for current and near future needs, but also that technological difficulties had been overcome with technological progress. After several months of technological breakthroughs, the Navy's senior management approved the construction of this type of warship.\n\n\ The Lyra plan completed the design of the basic configuration and some subsystems before the disconnection of the stargate. The remaining technical details were lost with the disconnection of Jefferson Company. The Ziz class was the result of a significant redesign after being taken over by the Jefferson branch in the capital of Argon and the reconnected Jefferson branch, based on the Lyra plan. \n\n\Characteristics:\033#99e03b29#Neutron Extravasation Armor\033X\n\The expensive neutron tube embedded armor cannot be mass-produced, so a new type of armor that is not as expensive is widely used by Ziz. Although it is not as efficient as neutron tube embedded armor, neutron extravasation armor has a characteristic,\033#99ffd300#Neutron Resonance\033X Neutrons in neutron extravasation armor, when bombarded with extremely high energy, will transform into a resonant state and form a brief quantum transition channel with neighboring neutrons, which can be continuously transmitted. This effect can be seen to some extent as a degraded version of the neutron tube network. In this state, high-energy weapons like\033#99ffd300#ATF Main gun\033X Part of the thermal effects generated by the bombardment of the armor will be transmitted at high speeds in a stable resonant state. According to laboratory tests, this resonant state can reduce approximately \033#99e03b29#50%\033X\ of the damage caused by high-energy weapons. At the same time, the adjusted force field(shield) can transfer some of the high-energy beam's energy to the armor within a safe range and complete absorption.</t>
			<t id="4">Ziz</t>
			<t id="5">Garuda</t>
			<t id="6">(Garuda){993512,8}</t>
			<t id="7">The pinnacle of the design by the design team of the Ziz class was to explore the limits of this ship. In a sense, the birth of this warship was a response to some critics questioning whether the Ziz class could resist Asgard. Unlike the Ziz class, the entire hull of this warship was replaced with expensive embedded neutron tube frames, which have extremely high resistance to high-energy weapon direct fire. However, the terrifying high price of this warship has deterred even the Argon Navy, and its characteristic are almost always a provocation to the Terran Protector.This battleship has only produced one prototype ship. After careful consideration, the federal leadership has decided to gift this battleship to the legendary hero who made a famous contribution to the federal history and made remarkable achievements in the battle against Xenon in the x universe.\n\n\Characteristic:\033#9900ffff#Unique\033X\n\This is the unique warship in the universe, with its engine emitting a unique light. \n\n\Characteristic:\033#99e03b29#Embedded neutron tube frame hull\033X\n\The most direct manifestation of the terrifying energy transfer efficiency of the neutron tube frame isThe armor of this warship can absorb more \033#99ffd300#high-energy rays\033X\ than the Ziz class,It does not need to rely on the resonant state of high-energy bombardment like Ziz to create energy transfer channels. The efficient heat dissipation capability also enables this warship to install directional plasma jet weapons on any large turret.\n\n\Characteristic:\033#99e03b29#Neutron tube network\033X\n\The neutron tube framework, like human blood vessels, can form stable channels inside, and programmable nanomaterials are transported at high speed within the channel network to repaired hull damage.(When hull is below 100% and above 50%, recover hull at a rate of 1% every 5 seconds. When hull is below 50% and above 18%, recover hull at a rate of 1% every 3 seconds. When hull is below 18% and above 1%, recover hull at a rate of 1% every 1 second).\n\n\Characteristic:\033#99e03b29#Emergency Repair Agreement\033X\(Not yet implemented) \n\ When the damage to the warship is too severe, the system will automatically initiate an emergency repair agreement, which involves removing parts from the weapon system to repair the damage to the hull and repairing it to the maximum extent possible.\n\n\Characteristic:\033#99e03b29#Indestructible\033X\(Not yet implemented) \n\ The main control core and energy core of this warship are difficult to truly destroy, and even if the ship is subjected to a devastating blow, there is still a possibility of repair.</t>
			<t id="8">Garuda</t>
		</page>
		<page id="993513" title="wapon_arg_ziz_jet" descr="wapon_arg_ziz_jet" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">plasma jet projector</t>
			<t id="2">(plasma jet projector) {993513,4}</t>
			<t id="3"> Heating a low-quality object to an incredible temperature and projecting it with a strong magnetic field, the plasma envelops the projectile and releases a large amount of energy through contact with the object. This is the principle of a basic plasma cannon. However, as the flight distance increases, the projectile will gradually be consumed by the enveloped plasma, and the magnetic field surrounding the projectile gradually weakens, ultimately dissipating along with the plasma. However, if the high-temperature plasma is accelerated to a very high speed and directly projected to form a jet, the accuracy and speed of plasma projection can be greatly improved. Based on this theory, a directional plasma projector has been developed. In fact, the technical principle of this weapon is not complex, and the key to the difficulty of using a plasma jet is that the turbulence generated by the plasma during the circulation acceleration process will escape from the constraints, The generation of extremely strong ionizing radiation and extremely high temperatures can have a destructive impact on weapon systems. The plasma loses its restraint before launch and collides with the cabin wall, ultimately leading to accidents. Jefferson and Argonia Materials Research developed a structure called a neutron tube frame a long time ago, but the Jefferson branch, which lost its headquarters, only recently commercialized it. The lattice, embedded in the armor, greatly improves the material's heat exchange efficiency and is evenly distributed among all lattice structures. Placing it on the inner wall of the plasma accelerator can effectively absorb plasma turbulence, The directional plasma flow projector can withstand higher power shooting, but unfortunately, this expensive material is difficult to produce on a large scale, so it cannot be used as an armor plate. The ionizing radiation generated by higher power plasma jets is still deadly. Therefore, the design of the Ziz class has changed the original weapon layout and structure. Now, this type of weapon is placed in an independent unmanned module, powered by external power, and maintenance work is handed over to experienced remote control maintenance technicians. Currently, only the Ziz class has sufficient conditions to safely use this powerful weapon.</t>
			<t id="4">plasma jet projector</t>
			<t id="5">ziz maingun</t>
			<t id="6">(ziz maingun){993513,8}</t>
			<t id="7">A special weapon with much lower firepower than the normal version of the Behemoth main gun. Due to the fact that most of the output power of the Ziz class weapons is occupied by the jet system, the main gun power is strictly limited. As for why the fully armed Ziz needs to install these two unimportant main guns, Navy officials who do not want to be named revealed that due to the frequent occurrence of the Ziz class in fierce battles, some captains have forgotten to control the combat distance due to excessive engagement in combat. The Navy logistics department has repeatedly complained about the increased workload and cost of repairing unnecessary damage to the Ziz class.The federal navy had to strengthen captain training and install two main guns, mainly to remind the captain of the combat distance. Some media have raised questions about this matter with the federal navy, but all similar questions have been ignored by the navy spokesperson.</t>
			<t id="8">ziz maingun</t>
		</page>
	</add>	
</diff>