<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<language id="44">
<page id="22121" title="FAS" descr="FAS mod" voice="no">
 <t id="19">FAS Federal Heavy Cruiser</t>
 <t id="20">The FAS Federal Heavy Cruiser is one of the main battleships in the Earth Federal Fleet. It features powerful firepower, heavy armor, and a comprehensive defense system. It is mainly used for frontline combat, fleet command, and storming important targets. It can play a key strategic deterrence and practical role in interstellar battlefields. Equipped with various advanced weapons and equipment, its overall combat effectiveness is far superior to that of light cruisers.</t>
 <t id="21">Federal Heavy Cruiser Sublight Engine</t>
 <t id="34">The Federal Heavy Cruiser is equipped with multiple sets of high-power sublight engines. Although slightly less flexible than the engines of light cruisers, they have stronger output power, which can provide stable and continuous power for the huge hull. This ensures that the warship has sufficient speed and endurance in interstellar navigation, and can support long-term battlefield deployment and long-distance maneuvering.</t>
 <t id="22">Federal Heavy Cruiser Dual Energy Cannon</t>
 <t id="23">The dual energy cannon of the Federal Heavy Cruiser is its core offensive weapon, installed at key positions of the hull. Compared with the same type of weapons on light cruisers, it has stronger energy output, longer range, and greater destructive power. It can cause devastating damage to large enemy ships, solid fortifications, etc., and is the main firepower output point in fleet battles.</t>
 <t id="24">Federal Heavy Cruiser MW-5050 Dual Fifty Automatic Turret</t>
 <t id="25">Federal Heavy Cruisers generally carry MW-5050 dual fifty automatic turrets as close-in defense weapons. The number of these turrets is more than that of light cruisers, distributed in various key parts of the hull. With high rate of fire and precise automatic aiming capability, they can effectively intercept incoming enemy aircraft, missiles, and small combat units at close range, building a dense close-in defense fire network for the warship.</t>
 <t id="26">Federal Heavy Cruiser Kinetic Barrier Generator</t>
 <t id="27">The kinetic barrier generator equipped on the Federal Heavy Cruiser has more advanced performance. The generated shield has much stronger defense strength than that of light cruisers (if light cruisers are equipped with it). It can withstand multiple attacks from enemy heavy weapons, greatly reducing the damage to the hull, and providing reliable protection for the warship in fierce battlefield confrontations, which is an important support for its survival capability.</t>
</page>
</language>

