<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff>
	<add sel="/language">
<page id="2025071305" title="ccunsc" descr="ccunsc mod" voice="no">
<t id="1">UNSC paris</t>
<t id="2">"Париж" является флагманским кораблем Космического командования (United Nations Space Command). По состоянию на 2559 год, "Париж" является крупнейшим и наиболее совершенным военным кораблем в UNSC. По заказу Управления военно-морской разведки (ONI) и тайно построенный в Облаке Оорта, он использует технологии, заимствованные у "Ковенанта" и "Предтеч", и на его завершение ушло несколько лет. Значительное количество десантников находятся на борту "Парижа" для прохождения службы.</t>
<t id="3">XR2 Borealis Field S81/X-DFR Nuclear Fusion Propulsor</t>
<t id="4">An assembly consisting of a main fusion engine beneath the fusion reactor and two auxiliary engine units. The city-sized engine module took fifteen years to design, construct, and test. The slipspace engine is the Mark X Macedon/Z-PROTOTYPE #78720HDS Revision 2.1, mounted on a remote托架, which is derived from a recovered Forerunner slipspace engine core, capable of exiting slipspace with considerable precision. The engine powers itself by directly absorbing energy from the vacuum bubble, with vacuum energy being independent of the ship's own fusion engine power supply. Due to incompatibility between Forerunner slipspace drives and UNSC conventional power systems and related data feedback, a全新 engine interconnect module based on Covenant engine control limiter modules was installed on the paris.</t>
<t id="5">Misriah MG-44N Heavy Energy Shield Generator</t>
<t id="6">A flagship-class shield generator produced by Misriah Armory</t>
<t id="7">CR-03B Series-8 Magnetic Accelerator Cannon</t>
<t id="8">Capable of launching various artillery shells, cargo packages, and suicide vehicles with dedicated payloads.</t>
<t id="9">M2551 "Ballista" Magnetic Accelerator Cannon Array</t>
<t id="10">The Mark 2511 Ballista-type MAC cannon can fire 15-centimeter projectiles with a kinetic energy of up to 1.1 gigajoules. It features five linearly arranged magnetic coils, each requiring separate charging before firing. It also needs to cool down after each shot, achieved by opening radial vents on the upper part of the barrel. Weapon operation is conducted from an operations station to the left of the MAC cannon.</t>
<t id="11">M85 Sickle Anti-Air Turret</t>
<t id="12">The M85 Sickle is a low-profile, belt-fed, dual-barreled, anti-air/anti-craft weapon. It is designed to be mounted on orbital or suborbital military bases as well as the external hull of warships. Unlike the M71 Sickle, it is not limited to ground defense, as the fully sealed casing of the M85 allows it to be used in a vacuum.</t>
<t id="13">M965 "Bastion" 70mm Caliber Point-Defense Gun</t>
<t id="14">It is the most commonly used shipborne defense system in the UNSC Navy, all operated automatically by computers or AIs, as human reaction speeds are insufficient to fully handle its operation. Its turret consists of dual or quadruple 50mm rapid-fire coilguns and a target scanner. This defense system is used to counter close-range threats, including enemy aircraft and plasma torpedoes. Each turret automatically analyzes the current threat level to switch between sub-caliber armor-piercing rounds and proximity-fused fragmentation rounds, maximizing its operational efficiency.</t>
<t id="15">M42 "Archer" Missile Launch Pod</t>
<t id="16">UNSC paris-class Missile Launcher 1 Information</t>
<t id="17">M75 "Longsword" Missile Launch Pod</t>
<t id="18">UNSC paris-class Missile Launcher 2 Information</t>
<t id="19">M96 "Roar" Missile Launch Pod</t>
<t id="20">UNSC paris-class Missile Launcher 3 Information</t>
<t id="21">M97 "Javelin" Guided Missile Launch System</t>
<t id="22">UNSC paris-class Missile Launcher 4 Information</t>
<t id="23">Tactical Nuclear Missile Launcher</t>
<t id="24">UNSC paris-class Missile Launcher 5 Information</t>
<t id="25">M42 "Archer" Missile</t>
<t id="26">UNSC paris-class Missile 1 Information</t>
<t id="27">M75 "Longsword" Missile</t>
<t id="28">UNSC paris-class Missile 2 Information</t>
<t id="29">M96 "Roar" Missile</t>
<t id="30">UNSC paris-class Missile 3 Information</t>
<t id="31">M97 "Javelin" Guided Missile</t>
<t id="32">UNSC paris-class Missile 4 Information</t>
<t id="33">Shiva Tactical Nuclear Missile</t>
<t id="34">UNSC paris-class Missile 5 Information</t>
</page>
	</add>
</diff>