<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff>
	<add sel="/language">
<page id="2025071305" title="ccunsc" descr="ccunsc mod" voice="no">
<t id="1">Париж</t>
<t id="2">Compared to other frigates in the UNSC Navy, the Парис heavy frigate has extremely high operational efficiency. When facing the powerful Covenant enemies, pure firepower output is far more important than transport capacity and protection level. As a result, by the end of the Human-Covenant War, the Парис had come to dominate the construction scale of frigates. With a seasoned crew team at the helm, the Парис frigate can even engage in extremely dangerous confrontations with Covenant battlecruisers, inflicting damage on them through a series of strategic strikes and feint tactics.</t>
<t id="3">Nuclear Fusion Engine</t>
<t id="4">Париж Engine Information</t>
<t id="5">Мисрия МС-44Н - Генератор тяжелого энергетического щита</t>
<t id="6">Генератор щита флагманского класса, произведенный оружейной корпорацией Мисрии</t>
<t id="7">65P8V1 Magnetic Accelerator Cannon</t>
<t id="8">Париж Main Gun Information</t>
<t id="9">Париж Heavy Cannon</t>
<t id="10">Париж Heavy Cannon Information</t>
<t id="11">M870 Bastion Point-Defense Gun</t>
<t id="12">This point-defense gun is used to counter threats from incoming fighters, landing craft, and plasma torpedoes. Additionally, based on threat analysis of the current target, it can switch between firing 50mm armor-piercing rounds or 50mm proximity-fused fragmentation rounds to achieve maximum effectiveness. It is generally configured as twin or quadruple mounts, paired with a targeting scanner, to function as a turret. Due to being equipped on various warships, the M870 Bastion-type point-defense gun has become a relatively common piece of equipment in the UNSC fleet.</t>
<t id="13">Париж Point Defense 2</t>
<t id="14">Париж Point Defense 2 Information</t>
<t id="15">M58 Archer Missile Pod</t>
<t id="16">Париж Missile Launcher 1 Information</t>
<t id="17">M2475 Shiva-class Nuclear Missile</t>
<t id="18">Париж Missile Launcher 2 Information</t>
<t id="19">Harpoon Nuclear Missile Silo</t>
<t id="20">Париж Missile Launcher 3 Information</t>
<t id="21">Париж Missile Launcher 4</t>
<t id="22">Париж Missile Launcher 4 Information</t>
<t id="23">Париж Missile Launcher 5</t>
<t id="24">Париж Missile Launcher 5 Information</t>
<t id="25">Париж Missile 1</t>
<t id="26">Париж Missile 1 Information</t>
<t id="27">Париж Missile 2</t>
<t id="28">Париж Missile 2 Information</t>
<t id="29">Париж Missile 3</t>
<t id="30">Париж Missile 3 Information</t>
<t id="31">Париж Missile 4</t>
<t id="32">Париж Missile 4 Information</t>
<t id="33">Париж Missile 5</t>
<t id="34">Париж Missile 5 Information</t>
</page>
	</add>
</diff>