<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff>
	<add sel="/language">
<page id="2025071309" title="ccunsc" descr="ccunsc mod" voice="no">
<t id="1">UNSC Марафон</t>
<t id="2">Although the Марафон heavy cruiser was designed as a purely combat vessel, during the darkest hours of the war against the Covenant, many ships of this class were entrusted with the role of flagship. Even though they could not fully match the Covenant's cruisers of the same class, their powerful equipment and impressive resilience still posed a serious threat to the enemy, helping humanity endure nearly three decades of brutal war and continuing to fight in the evolving conflicts after the war.</t>
<t id="3">Nuclear Fusion Engine</t>
<t id="4">UNSC Марафон Engine Information</t>
<t id="5">UNSC Марафон Shield</t>
<t id="6">UNSC Марафон Shield Information</t>
<t id="7">49F9A1 Magnetic Accelerator Cannon</t>
<t id="8">UNSC Марафон Main Gun Information</t>
<t id="9">M66 Sentry Autocannon</t>
<t id="10">A heavy shipborne cannon equipped on New Era-class Heavy Aircraft Carriers and Late Autumn-class Heavy Cruisers; it is also fitted on the UNSC Pillar of Autumn, which was modified for Operation Red Flag.</t>
<t id="11">M810 Spiral Point-Defense Gun</t>
<t id="12">The M810 Spiral Point-Defense Gun is also known as the AAA Point-Defense Gun or Spiral Close-In Weapon System. This point-defense gun was used in both human counter-terrorism wars and the Human-Covenant War, and was still in use during the Battle of Psi Serpentis in 2543. It is described as "spinning and heating," indicating that the M810 Spiral Point-Defense Gun is a multi-barreled Gatling-style cannon. Like other point-defense guns used by the UNSC, the M810 can also be controlled by shipboard computers or artificial intelligence.</t>
<t id="13">UNSC Марафон Point Defense 2</t>
<t id="14">UNSC Марафон Point Defense 2 Information</t>
<t id="15">M40 Longbow Missile Pod</t>
<t id="16">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 1 Information</t>
<t id="17">M58 Archer Missile Pod</t>
<t id="18">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 2 Information</t>
<t id="19">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 3</t>
<t id="20">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 3 Information</t>
<t id="21">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 4</t>
<t id="22">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 4 Information</t>
<t id="23">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 5</t>
<t id="24">UNSC Марафон Missile Launcher 5 Information</t>
<t id="25">UNSC Марафон Missile 1</t>
<t id="26">UNSC Марафон Missile 1 Information</t>
<t id="27">UNSC Марафон Missile 2</t>
<t id="28">UNSC Марафон Missile 2 Information</t>
<t id="29">UNSC Марафон Missile 3</t>
<t id="30">UNSC Марафон Missile 3 Information</t>
<t id="31">UNSC Марафон Missile 4</t>
<t id="32">UNSC Марафон Missile 4 Information</t>
<t id="33">UNSC Марафон Missile 5</t>
<t id="34">UNSC Марафон Missile 5 Information</t>
</page>
	</add>
</diff>