<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content id="Aircraft_carrier_Goliath" name="Aircraft carrier Goliath" description="This mod adds a new aircraft carrier Goliath for Argon Federation.&#13;&#10;
After the reconnection of the stargate, the Argon Federation bought many useful new technologies from the lost colonies. With the gradual recovery of the Federal economy, the Argon Federation began to plan to build a new type of aircraft carrier, which was different from the Colossus class that abandoned many functions for mass production in a special period. Goliath was designed as a flagship at the beginning. In addition to having a huge hangar, There are also eight catapults built for rapid takeoff. According to tradition, the first aircraft carrier of this type was named Argon One and deployed to patrol in the Argon-Prime.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;
How can I get it?&#13;&#10;
This aircraft carrier is not for sale like ATF Asgard and ATF Syn, but you can broght blueprints in Argon faction representative, or you can landing &quot;argon one&quot;(I addied a NPC's Goliath class) in Argon Prime." author="BZDBQG" version="120" date="2023-09-07" save="0" lastupdate="1694084414">
  <text language="7" name="Aircraft carrier Goliath" description="Этот мод добавляет новый авианосец Голиаф для Федерации Аргон.&#13;&#10;
После восстановления звездных врат Аргонская федерация приобрела много полезных новых технологий у потерянных колоний. С постепенным восстановлением федеральной экономики Федерация Аргон начала планировать строительство авианосца нового типа, который отличался бы от класса Колосс, который отказался от многих функций ради массового производства в особый период. Изначально Голиаф проектировался как флагманский корабль. В дополнение к огромному ангару, здесь также установлены восемь катапульт для быстрого взлета. Согласно традиции, первый авианосец этого типа был назван 'Голиаф 1' и направлен на патрулирование в Аргон Прайм.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;
Как я могу его получить?&#13;&#10;
Этот авианосец не продается, как  Асгард и Син, но вы можете приобрести чертежи у представителя фракции Аргон или совершить посадку на 'Голиаф 1'.;(Я добавил класс NPC Голиаф) в Аргон Прайм." author="BZDBQG"></text>
</content>
