<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff>
	<add sel="/language">
		<page id="654612" title="lint_ter_frigate" descr="lint_ter_frigate" voice="no">
			<!-- Ship -->
			<t id="1">Commissioned not long after the Jump Gates shut down, the (Akita){20101, 64601}-class of frigates were designed during a period of uncertainty. Due to the restructuring of USC and ATF into the Terran Protectorate and the aftermath of recent war with the Commonwealth, Terran navy logistics were heavily strained with repairing and refitting tasks. The heavily strained logistics combined with the economic shock of losing the Torus Aeternal created a environment where a cheap and long enduring class of vessels were desired in replacing heavier classes of vessels for patrolling the outer rim of Sol. Given the urgency, Terran engineers based most systems of the (Akita){20101, 64601}-class on the mostly finalized Maccana(same as seen in X3AP)-class frigates to reduce cost and design time.\n\nAlthough designed for anti-piracy patrol and freighter escort, for the majority of its service history the (Akita){20101, 64601}-class frigates saw an unexpectedly peaceful Sol. Most of the newly built (Akita){20101, 64601}-classes were soon mothballed and stored in the outer rim stations. Even the ones remained active served more commonly as military transports rather than its orginal roles. As the gates reopened however, (Akita){20101, 64601}-class of ships saw a much heavier usage within both the Pioneer Initiative and Terran Protectorate. The long endurance of the (Akita){20101, 64601}-class made it the perfect frontier vessel for usage in the then empty Segairs systems. The same endurance also made it the perfect escort for Protectorate fleets' expeditions deep into Commonwealth space.</t>

			<t id="2">When the Pioneer Initiative was first established, a number of (Akita){20101, 64601}-class frigates were assigned into the initiative. Although the Pionners were satisfied with the anti-fighter performance of the (Akita){20101, 64601}-class, they soon wanted a class of dedicated anti-capital ships to complement the fleet of (Osaka){20101, 60201}-classes. After a short examination period, a descision was made to refit existing (Akita){20101, 64601}-classes for the role and thus the (Kitsune){20101, 13201} refit program was established. Although the program is still under devolepment and testing, early combat results are promising and plans are already being drawn to produce new (Kitsune){20101, 13201}-class directly.\n\nCompared to the (Akita){20101, 64601}-class, (Kitsune){20101, 13201}-class refits featured a much more distinguished anti-capital ships ability. The refits lost their upper deck turrets in favour of torpedo launchers while its extended fuel and cargo storage were also removed for more ammunition capacity.</t>

			<!-- Weapon -->
			<t id="10">Hull-fixed Crusie Missile Launcher</t>
			<t id="11">Hull-fixed Torpedo Launcher</t>

			<!-- Ammo -->
			<t id="200">General-purpose Cruise Missile</t>
			<t id="201">(General-purpose Cruise Missile Mk1){654612, 200} {20111,101}</t>
			<t id="202">(General-purpose Cruise Missile Mk2){654612, 200} {20111,201}</t>
			<t id="210">Agile Cruise Missile</t>

			<t id="300">High-yield Torpedo</t>
			<t id="301">(High-yield Torpedo Mk1){654612,300} {20111,101}</t>
			<t id="302">(High-yield Torpedo Mk2){654612,300} {20111,201}</t>
			<t id="310">High-velocity Shield-bypass Torpedo</t>

			<!-- Ammo Desc -->
			<!-- <t id="1200">(General-purpose Cruise Missile){654612, 200}</t>
			<t id="1210">A experimentally modified verison of the (General-purpose Cruise Missile){654612, 200} with greatly improved manoeuvrability at the cost of range. Although largely untested, Segairs Pionners are more than happy to provide this design to its allies.</t>

			<t id="1300">(High-yield Torpedo){654612, 300}</t>
			<t id="1310">A torpedo featuring a experimental warhead design. The warhead of this torpedo have two sections, first section is used in breaking down localized enemy shielding while the second is delivered as the payload. The shield-breaking section is effectivly a cell of high-energy plasma that</t> -->

			<!--VRO iShield-->
			<t id="1000">IG L - (Akita){20101, 64601} Interal Generator</t>
			<t id="1001">IG L - (Kitsune){20101, 13201} Interal Generator</t>
		</page>
	</add>
</diff>
