<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff>
	<add sel="/language">
<page id="2025071308" title="ccunsc" descr="ccunsc mod" voice="no">
<t id="1">UNSC Тантос</t>
<t id="2">It was designed as an aggressive attack cruiser, and together with the Io-class light cruisers, it was part of the UNSC's military restructuring plan to counter colonial rebellions. It replaced the obsolete Victoria-class armored cruisers, entering service during the Epsilon Eridani Insurrection, where it helped eliminate the rebels' inferior fleet and participated in the Farkiri Independence War. At that time, it was regarded as one of the most heavily armed and well-armored warships in the UNSC fleet. Its crew spaces were notorious for being cramped and uncomfortable, as most of the ship's space was occupied by weapon systems, leaving little room for them. Coupled with high maintenance standards, it was very unpopular among the crew, who nicknamed it the "Hell-class Cruiser" to mock the harsh living conditions on board. Over time, its onboard weaponry became outdated and was gradually phased out by the navy, finally ceasing production in 2512 and being replaced by the Marathon-class.</t>
<t id="3">Tresler GEN6-LTa</t>
<t id="4">UNSC Тантос Engine Information</t>
<t id="5">UNSC Тантос Shield</t>
<t id="6">UNSC Тантос Shield Information</t>
<t id="7">MarkIII LG22B1R5 Heavy Magnetic Accelerator Cannon</t>
<t id="8">UNSC Тантос Main Gun Information</t>
<t id="9">A2R1 Coilgun</t>
<t id="10">UNSC Тантос Heavy Cannon Information</t>
<t id="11">M800 Bulwark Point-Defense Gun</t>
<t id="12">It is the most commonly used shipborne defense system in the UNSC Navy, all operated automatically by computers or AIs, as human reaction speeds are insufficient to fully handle its operation. Its turret consists of dual or quadruple 50mm rapid-fire coilguns and a target scanner. This defense system is used to counter close-range threats, including enemy aircraft and plasma torpedoes. Each turret automatically analyzes the current threat level to switch between sub-caliber armor-piercing rounds and proximity-fused fragmentation rounds, maximizing its operational efficiency.</t>
<t id="13">M800 Bulwark Point-Defense Gun</t>
<t id="14">It is the most commonly used shipborne defense system in the UNSC Navy, all operated automatically by computers or AIs, as human reaction speeds are insufficient to fully handle its operation. Its turret consists of dual or quadruple 50mm rapid-fire coilguns and a target scanner. This defense system is used to counter close-range threats, including enemy aircraft and plasma torpedoes. Each turret automatically analyzes the current threat level to switch between sub-caliber armor-piercing rounds and proximity-fused fragmentation rounds, maximizing its operational efficiency.</t>
<t id="15">Ares Missile</t>
<t id="16">UNSC Тантос Missile Launcher 1 Information</t>
<t id="17">ATAF Missile Turret</t>
<t id="18">UNSC Тантос Missile Launcher 2 Information</t>
<t id="19">Fusion Rocket</t>
<t id="20">UNSC Тантос Missile Launcher 3 Information</t>
<t id="21">Shiva-class Nuclear Missile</t>
<t id="22">UNSC Тантос Missile Launcher 4 Information</t>
<t id="23">M42 Archer Missile Pod</t>
<t id="24">UNSC Тантос Missile Launcher 5 Information</t>
<t id="25">UNSC Тантос Missile 1</t>
<t id="26">UNSC Тантос Missile 1 Information</t>
<t id="27">UNSC Тантос Missile 2</t>
<t id="28">UNSC Тантос Missile 2 Information</t>
<t id="29">UNSC Тантос Missile 3</t>
<t id="30">UNSC Тантос Missile 3 Information</t>
<t id="31">UNSC Тантос Missile 4</t>
<t id="32">UNSC Тантос Missile 4 Information</t>
<t id="33">UNSC Тантос Missile 5</t>
<t id="34">UNSC Тантос Missile 5 Information</t>
</page>
	</add>
</diff>